vertitechnologygroup.com 2013-12-05

# Verti Technology Group

## Including for the RocketFuel Installer

_Updated 08/07/2011_

This Privacy Policy describes how and when Verti Technology Group ("Verti", "we", "us" or "our") collects, uses and shares your information when you use our Services. We respect your privacy and are concerned about how your personal information is shared and used. You acknowledge that you accept the terms of this privacy policy whenever you use any of our services or products, including without limitation the Verti RocketFuel Installer software, and our websites that post a link to this privacy policy, including [http://www.vertitechnologygroup.com](http://www.vertitechnologygroup.com/), ("Sites", "Services" or "Products").

You must be at least 18 years of age to use our Sites or Software. If you are under 18 years old, do not use our Sites and do not download our products.

This privacy policy covers our treatment of Personally Identifiable Information and other information we gather when you use our software or services or access our Sites. We are not responsible for, nor does this policy apply to, the practices of companies that we do not own or control, including our Partners, or to individuals we do not employ or manage. When using third-party software products or sites, you should read the applicable privacy policies of those providers explaining their privacy practices.

### Policy Overview.

We provide access on our Sites to free software we created (Software) for your computer as well as the opportunity to download third-party software.

Please carefully read this privacy policy so that you understand our online privacy practices, including those regarding information we collect, your choices regarding your information, and how we share and use your information.

We may at any time modify this privacy policy. If we modify this policy, we will post the changes or the changed version on our Sites homepages and other places we believe are appropriate. If we materially modify this policy, we will notify you by updating the date specified in the Updated line near the top of this privacy policy, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Personally Identifiable Information.

_Partner Offers_. During and after installation, you may be presented with offers to obtain products from our third-party partners ("Partners") which you may choose to reject or accept. Your participation is completely voluntary, and you are neither required to disclose to our Partners any information they request nor receive any products. Our products do not collect information that identifies you specifically or could be used to specifically identify, locate or contact you, such as your credit card number ("Personally Identifiable Information"), except as otherwise set forth in this privacy policy. However, we are not responsible if you provide your Personally Identifiable Information to our Partners, for example when responding to an offer from them in which you are interested.

_Voluntary Information_. We may keep a record of communication if you voluntarily contact us or submit information, for example, by requesting technical support. If you use the Customer Support or Contact sections or forms on our Sites, we will collect your name, email address, topic and any additional information you provide, although we use this information only to assist us in responding to your inquiry.

### Aggregate Information.

When you use our products, we may collect tracking information such as the type of operating system you use, the domain name of your Internet service provider (ISP), your IP address, details about your computer hardware, your browser type, pages you visited on our Sites, and the applications you have installed on your computer, including our and our Partners products. None of this information personally identifies you and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

When you install our products, we may create a unique anonymous identifier to track installations and enable functionality and features for specific customers who subscribe to our Products and Services. We do not link the information gathered by this anonymous identifier to your Personally Identifiable Information.

_Software Information_. Software installed on your computer has unique registry keys. We use this information to determine whether our program offers are compatible with software already present on your PC and to avoid duplication of installed programs. We do not link such gathered information to our users Personally Identifiable Information.

_Hardware Information_. Your computer stores hardware information that we use in order to identify your computers hardware configuration, including processor speed and available memory. We use this information to determine system compatibility and we do not link this information to your Personally Identifiable Information.

_Cookies_. A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser which is stored on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie terminates when you close your browser whereas a persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period afterwards. To remove persistent cookies, follow the directions provided in your Internet browser's Help file.

Some of our Partners' offers on our products may use cookies. We have no control over our Partners' privacy policies, their cookies, or the information collected and its use.

Cookies enable us and our Partners to track visits to our and their sites and stores by collecting information that describes which pages you have seen and measures certain traffic patterns, such as which of our Sites you have visited. We use this information to understand our users' habits so that we can improve each subsequent experience on a Site or better personalize the promotions, content, and banners presented to you. We do not store Personally Identifiable Information in our cookies nor do we link the information in our cookies to our users Personally Identifiable Information.

_Pixels_. Web beacons or pixels from us or third parties ("Pixels") are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, which track your online Web movement and which may be embedded virtually invisibly on Web pages. We and our Partners employ Pixels to better manage content on our Sites, but we do not link the information gathered by Pixels to our users' Personally Identifiable Information. With respect to third-party Pixels, these third parties may also use anonymous information about your visits to websites in order to improve their products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. Some of our Partners' offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our Partners' Pixels or how they use the information collected.

_MAC Address_. Your computer's MAC address is an alphanumeric identifier that acts as a unique code, assigned to your computer. We may collect your computer's MAC address when you install our products and use your computer's MAC address to track unique installations of our products. We do not link your computer's MAC address to any of your Personally Identifiable Information.

### Using Information.

We strive to make our Services more useful to you. By knowing information about you, we can deliver relevant products and offers. We maintain a secure database of all Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Sites.

_Third-Party Advertising_. Third parties advertise on our Sites, and we also contract with third parties to serve ads over the Internet. These third parties may serve ads about our or our Partners' products or services which, based on information collected about you, we or our Partners believe you may be interested in. These third party advertisers may use cookies and Pixels, including those collected on our Sites, to track session data about the ads you have seen and types of things in which you seem interested. These third parties may also use information about your visits to our Sites and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of the third-party advertising program at the Network Advertising Initiative website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. Opting out of a network means that the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns, but does not mean that you will no longer receive online advertising.

When you click on a third-party advertisers's link from our Sites, you will enter the third party's site for which we are not responsible. You should review the privacy statements of any other site you visit, because your usage of that site will be governed by that site’s privacy policy which may be different from our privacy policythose.

_Research_. We study users' interests and demographics. We also use server log files, cookies, pixels, and software checker information to better understand and serve you. We compile and analyze this information on an aggregated basis, and may share this aggregated data periodically with current and potential Partners, however we do not link this aggregated information to your Personally Identifiable Information.

### Sharing Your Information.

We may co-sponsor an offer with a Partner or our Partners may sponsor offers through our product. You should assume data collected when you provide information about yourself to obtain offer will be shared with or collected by a Partner. If an offer requires you to leave our Sites, our Partners may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. We do not control our Partners' sites or their privacy policies. This privacy policy does not cover our Partners' websites and information practices. Once you have voluntarily submitted information to our Partners, your Personally Identifiable Information is subject to their privacy policy. We have no liability or responsibility for any privacy policies other than our own or the use of any Personally Identifiable Information transferred to our Partners. If you no longer wish to be contacted by our Partners you must contact that Partner directly to opt out.

It is not possible to continually provide an exhaustive list of our Partners since they change from time to time. We aim to work with trustworthy Partners who offer high quality products or services of potential interest to you. If you are dissatisfied with one of our Partners, please contact us using our contact information provided below.

From time to time we work with third-parties when providing services to you. We will only share with third parties information necessary for them to provide the services you have requested.

Although we do not require you to provide Personally Identifiable Information during our installation process, you may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information when you voluntarily contact us or request our Partners' offers.

_Legal Disclosure_. We may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to contact, identify, or bring legal action against someone who, either intentionally or unintentionally, may be violating our policies or may be causing injury to or interference with our property, rights, users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose information as required by law when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to protect our rights, to comply with a judicial procedure related to our Sites, or for administrative and other purposes we feel may be necessary to maintain service or improve our products and services.

_Sale, Merger or Asset Transfer_. We may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets, including user information as one of the business assets involved in such transactions. In the event that we or all of our assets are acquired, user information, including any information collected through our Sites or products, would be one of those transferred assets.

### Your Choices

_Cookies_. By changing your browser preferences, you can choose to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you may be unable to use our products or services.

Because no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, we cannot guarantee or warrant that no information, including without limitation user information or Personally Identifiable Information, will ever be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

Only users 18 years or older are permitted under this privacy policy to use our products and services. We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13.

### Warranty Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability

YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES AND PRODUCTS IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. OUR SERVICES AND PRODUCTS (INCLUDING ALL CONTENT AND FUNCTIONS MADE AVAILABLE ON OR ACCESSED THROUGH OUR SITES) IS PROVIDED "AS IS." WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ABOUT: (1) ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT; OR (2) THE SERVER AND SOFTWARE THAT MAKES OUR SERVICES AVAILABLE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THAT IT IS FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER COMPONENTS THAT MAY HARM, INFECT, OR CAUSE DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT OR ANY OTHER PROPERTY WHEN YOU ACCESS, DOWNLOAD FROM, BROWSE, OR OTHERWISE USE OUR SITES OR PRODUCTS.

UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO OUR NEGLIGENCE, SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR SPECIAL DAMAGES RELATED TO THE USE OF, THE INABILITY TO USE, OR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENTS AND FUNCTIONS OF OUR SITES AND SERVICES, EVEN IF WE OR OUR REPRESENTATIVES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT SHALL OUR TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION (WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR TORT, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) EXCEED $10.00.

_Indemnification_. You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless us, our subsidiaries, affiliates and parent companies, and all of our and their directors, officers, employees, agents, information providers, licensors and licensees (collectively, "Indemnified Parties") from and against any and all liability, losses, claims and costs (including, without limitation, attorneys' fees and costs) in connection with any claim arising out of any breach by you of this privacy policy. You will cooperate as fully as reasonably required in our defense of any claim. We reserve the right, at our own expense, to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you and you shall not in any event settle any matter without our written consent.

_Questions and Concerns_. If you believe that we have not followed our privacy policy, or if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy or would like a written copy, please feel free to contact us by e-mailing us at [customersupport@vertitechnology.com](mailto:customersupport@vertitechnology.com) or writing to:

Verti Technology Group  
Attention: Customer Service  
10900 NE 8th Street, Suite 1000  
Bellevue, WA 98004
